AppBundle\Entity\Answer:
    answer1:
        textAnswer: '2'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question1"
    answer2:
        textAnswer: '3'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question1"
    answer3:
        textAnswer: '4'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question1"
    answer4:
        textAnswer: '4'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question2"
    answer5:
        textAnswer: '5'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question2"
    answer6:
        textAnswer: '0'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question3"
    answer7:
        textAnswer: '2'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question3"
    answer8:
        textAnswer: '6'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question4"
    answer9:
        textAnswer: '12'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question4"
    answer10:
        textAnswer: '60'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question4"
    answer11:
        textAnswer: '22'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question4"
    answer12:
        textAnswer: '30'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question5"
    answer13:
        textAnswer: '32'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question5"
    answer14:
        textAnswer: '2'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question5"
    answer15:
        textAnswer: '24'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question6"
    answer16:
        textAnswer: '50'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question6"
    answer17:
        textAnswer: '50'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question7"
    answer18:
        textAnswer: '0.5'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question7"
    answer19:
        textAnswer: '5.5'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question7"
    answer20:
        textAnswer: '2'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question8"
    answer21:
        textAnswer: '6'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question8"
    answer22:
        textAnswer: '4.5'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question8"
    answer23:
        textAnswer: '8'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question8"
    answer24:
        textAnswer: '5'
        correctly: false
        question: "@question8"
    answer25:
        textAnswer: '9.5'
        correctly: true
        question: "@question8"



